Guide to the Deane W. Malott papers, 1951-1964
Malott, Deane W. papers, 1951-1964
- Graduate School., 1951-52 (Box 8, Folder 32)
- Fellowships., 1951-53 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  Danforth Foundation; Ford Foundation; National Academy of Sciences - National Research Council; John Simon Guggenheim Memorial Foundation.
- Glasgow University., 1951 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  Lawrence, George H. M.
- University of Erlangen., 1951 (Box 8, Folder 35)
- General Education for the Four Contract Colleges. Gannett, Caroline Werner., 1953 (Box 8, Folder 36)
- Meetings with State Deans., 1951 (Box 8, Folder 37)
- Dept. of Military Science and Tactics., 1951-52 (Box 8, Folder 38)
- Air ROTC., 1951-53 (Box 8, Folder 39-41)
- Dept. of Physical Education and Athletics., 1952-53 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  Kane, Robert J.; Stassen, Harold E.; Smith, Lloyd P. Hofstra College; Springfield College.
- Dept. of Physical Education and Athletics., 1952-53 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  Kane, Robert J.; Smith, Lyman H.; McGovern, John T.; Atherton, May; Bronk, Detlev W.; Carlson, William S. Schoellkopf Field.
- Dept. of Physical Education and Athletics., 1951-52 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  Kane, Robert J.; Carlson, William S.; Purcell, William Gray.
- Naval ROTC., 1951-53 (Box 8, Folder 45-46)
- ROTC., 1951-53 (Box 8, Folder 47-48)
- Laboratory of Nuclear Studies., 1951-53 (Box 8, Folder 49)
  Newman, Floyd R.; Wilson, Robert R.
- Ivy League., 1953 (Box 8, Folder 50)
  Gubb, Larry E.; Kane, Robert J. National Collegiate Athletic Association; University of Pennsylvania; Televising of football.
- Ivy League., 1952-53 (Box 8, Folder 51)
  Emanuel, Victor; Wriston, Henry M.; Bullis, Gardner; Merrihew, L. A. H. National Collegiate Athletic Association; Televising of football.
- Ivy League., 1951-52 (Box 8, Folder 52)
  Wriston, Henry M.; Conant, James B.; Kirk, Gray son; Lonborg, Arthur C. National Collegiate Athletic Association; Televising of football.
- Ivy League., 1952 (Box 8, Folder 53)
  Conant, James B.; Parke, John S.; Becker, Neal Dow; Griswold, A. Whitney. Televising of football.
- Military Reserves., 1950-51 (Box 8, Folder 54)
- Universal Military Training. Parley, Hugh D. "U.M.T. - A Challenge to American Thinking: by DWM., 1953 (Box 8, Folder 55)
- Universal Military Training., 1952-53 (Box 8, Folder 56)
  "U.M.T. - A Challenge to American Thinking" by DWM; National Conference for Mobilization of Education; American Council on Education.
- Cornell Aeronautical Laboratory., 1951-53 (Box 8, Folder 57)
  O'Neil, John J.; Wright, Theodore P.
- Cornell Aeronautical Laboratory., 1951 (Box 8, Folder 58)
  O'Neil, John J.; Furnas, Clifford C.
- Summer Session. Stutz, Frederick H., 1951-53 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Social Science Research Center., 1950-53 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  Williams, Robin M.; Morse, Chandler.
- University Testing and Service Bureau., 1951-53 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Social Science Research Center -Executive Committee., 1952 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Lilly Endowment., 1951 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  Emerson, Willard I.; Parker, Albert G.
- Carnegie Corporation., 1951 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Cornell Plantations., [1944-45] 1951-53 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  Adams, Bristow; Rockwell, George H.; MacDaniels, Laurence H.
- Infirmary and Clinic., 1951-53 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  Committee on Hospitalization and Medical Care.
- Cornell United Religious Work., 1953 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  Mendenhall, William W.; Taylor, Myron C.; Meigs, Robert B.
- Cornell United Religious Work., 1952 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  Mendenhall, William W.; Burtt, Edwin A.; Danforth, William H.; Alien, Lucile.
- Cornell United Religious Work., 1952-53 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  Mendenhall, William W.
- Cornell United Religious Work., 1951-52 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  Mendenhall, William W.; Rockefeller, Nelson A. Hazen Foundation; National Conference of Christians and Jews.
- Cornell United Religious Work., 1951 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  Mendenhall, William W.; Kelsey, Lincoln D.; Dall, Jes Jessen.
- Cornell Alumni Fund., 1951-53 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  Rockwell, George H.; Bradley, Hunt; Flickinger, William C.
- Alumni Office., 1951 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  Hoi lister, Solomon C.; Wade, Harry V.; Colman, Charles C.
- Alumni Office., 1951 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  Emerson, Willard I.; Brewer, R. Selden.
- Alumni Office., 1951 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  Emerson, Willard I.; Brewer, R. Selden; Treman, Robert E.; Wade, Harry V.
- Alumni Office., 1951-52 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  Emerson, Willard I.; Swirbul, William R.; Noyes, Jansen; Wade, Harry V.; Sullivan, Frank; McGovern, John T.; Brewer, R. Selden; Gannett, Frank E.
- Alumni Office. Pennington, John; Brewer, R. Selden; Farr, Newton C., 1952 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Alumni Office., 1952 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  Newman, Floyd R.
- Alumni Office. Dean, Daniel., 1952 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Alumni Office., 1952 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  Geer, William C.; Acker, Ernest R.; Woolley, Virginia. Paraguay.
- Alumni Office., 1952 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  Leinroth, Eugene A.; Newman, Floyd R.; Emanuel, Victor; Priest, Alice L.
- Alumni Office., 1952-53 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  Priest, Alice L.; Mills, Adelbert P.; LeBoeuf, Randall J.
- Alumni Office., 1953 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  Grohmann, H. Victor; Bache, Harold L.; Cornell, Ezra; Olin, John M.; Purcell, Robert W. Cornell College.
- Alumni Office., 1953 (Box 9, Folder 26)
- Alumni., 1951 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  War Alumnus certificates.
- Cornell Interfraternity Alumni Association., 1952-53 (Box 9, Folder 28)
- Scholarships and Grants., 1950-52 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  Cornell National Scholarship Committee.
- Scholarships and Grants., 1951-52 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  Emerson, Willard I. Cornell Alumni Club Scholarships.
- Scholarships and Grants., 1952 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  Pistilli, Philip. Teagle Foundation.
- Scholarships and Grants., 1952-53 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  Alfred P. Sloan Foundation.
- Alfred P. Sloan National Scholarship Program., 1952-53 (Box 9, Folder 33)
- President's Tuition Scholarships., 1951-53 (Box 9, Folder 34)
- Foreign Students scholarship., 1951 (Box 9, Folder 35)
- Prizes., 1952-53 (Box 9, Folder 36)
- Messenger Lectures., 1951-52 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  von Karman, Theodore.
- Messenger Lectures. Krutch, Joseph Wood., 1951-52 (Box 9, Folder 38)
- Messenger Lectures., 1952-53 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  Kendrick, M. Slade.
- Division of Extramural Courses., 1951-52 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  Smith, W. A.
- 4-H Clubs., 1951 (Box 9, Folder 41)
- Vacation Schedules., 1951-52 (Box 9, Folder 42)
- Educational Exchange., 1952 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  Cordell Hull Foundation for International Education.
- Visiting Professorships., 1951-53 (Box 9, Folder 44)
- State University of New York., 1951-53 (Box 9, Folder 45)
- State University of New York - Finances. Dean, Arthur H.; Wright, Theodore P.; Garside, Charles; Frodin, Reuben., 1951-52 (Box 9, Folder 46)
- State University of New York - Finances. Long Island Poultry Association., 1952-53 (Box 9, Folder 47)
- State University of New York - Finances. New York State Veterinary College., 1951-52 (Box 9, Folder 48)
- State University of New York. Carlson, William S., 1951-53 (Box 9, Folder 49)
- State University of New York Faculty Council., 1951-53 (Box 9, Folder 50)
- State University of New York - Student Housing., 1951 (Box 9, Folder 51)
- State University of New York - President. Carlson, William S.; Garside, Charles., 1951-52 (Box 9, Folder 52)
- State University of New York., 1951-52 (Box 9, Folder 53)
  Meigs, Robert B. Legislation.
- State University of New York., 1951-53 (Box 9, Folder 54)
  Tolley, William P.; Pfann, George R. Legislation.
- State University of New York. Legislation., 1953 (Box 9, Folder 55)
- Public Relations, Gifts, Budget., 1952 (Box 9, Folder 56)
- State University of New York - Cornell University Relationships., 1950-51 (Box 9, Folder 57)
- State University of New York Publications., 1951 (Box 9, Folder 58)
- State University of New York Annual Reports., 1951-52 (Box 9, Folder 59)
- State University of New York -Statistical Information., 1952-53 (Box 9, Folder 60)
- State University of New York - Personnel., 1951-53 (Box 9, Folder 61)
- State University of New York - Annual Reports., 1951 (Box 9, Folder 62)
- State University Association., 1951 (Box 9, Folder 63)
- State University of New York -Miscellaneous Information., 1951-53 (Box 9, Folder 64)
  Committee on State University Matters.
- State University of New York -Miscellaneous Information. Garside, Charles. Committee on State University Matters., 1951 (Box 9, Folder 65)
- State University of New York -Miscellaneous Information., 1951 (Box 9, Folder 66)
- New York State Education Dept. Nyquist, Ewald B., 1951-52 (Box 9, Folder 67)
- New York State Education Dept. Nyquist, Ewald B. Degrees., 1951-52 (Box 9, Folder 68)
- New York State Education Dept. Nyquist, Ewald B. Degrees., 1952-53 (Box 9, Folder 69)
- New York State Education Dept., 1952 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  Nyquist, Ewald B. Degrees.
- A Miscellaneous., 1954-55 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  Acker, Ernest R.; Bradley, Hunt; Andrae, William C. American Physical Society; American Association of University Women; American University; National Committee for the Aaronsburg Story; International Association of Ithaca; Cosmopolitan House.
- Accommodations., 1953 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- American Council on Education., 1953-55 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  Morrill, J. L.; Adams, Arthur S.
- American Council of Learned Societies., 1954 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Applicants for Jobs., 1953-55 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  Fanta, Arthur W.
- Association of American Universities., 1954 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Association of Colleges and Universities of the State of New York., 1953-55 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Association of Land-Grant Colleges and State Universities., 1953-55 (Box 10, Folder 9-10)
- B Miscellaneous., 1953-55 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  Becker, Harry; Verity, Calvin. American University of Beirut.
- Bethlehem Steel Company., 1953 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- C Miscellaneous., 1954-55 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  Carpenter, Walter S. Chicago Cornell Club; Lynah Rink; CBS Foundation.
- Carnegie Corporation., 1954 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  Noyes, Nicholas H.
- Citizenship Clearing House., 1954 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  Williams, George H.
- Conferences., 1953-55 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  Danzig, Phillip I.; Bunche, Ralph.
- D Miscellaneous., 1954-55 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- E Miscellaneous., 1953-55 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  Emerson, Edwin; White, Andrew Dickson; Emerson, Willard I.
- F Miscellaneous., 1954 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Ford Foundation., 1955 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  Gaither, H. Rowan.
- Ford Foundation., 1953-54 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- G Miscellaneous., 1955 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  Grasselli, Caesar A. General Mills, Inc.
- General Electric Company., 1953-55 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  Reed, Philip D.; Cordiner, Ralph J.
- General Motors Corporation., 1955 (Box 10, Folder 24)
- H Miscellaneous., 1954-55 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  Hesburgh, Theodore M. Hebrew University.
- H Miscellaneous., 1953-54 (Box 10, Folder 26)
- Hoover Report (The Commission on Organization of the Executive Branch of the Government)., 1954-55 (Box 10, Folder 27)
- I Miscellaneous., 1954-55 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  Ithaca College.
- Institute of International Education., 1955 (Box 10, Folder 29)
- Ithaca, New York., 1954-55 (Box 10, Folder 30)
- J Miscellaneous., 1954 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  Javits, Jacob K.
- K Miscellaneous., 1953-55 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  Kudner, Arthur H. Kresge Foundation.
- L Miscellaneous., 1954-55 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  Linowitz, Sol M.
- M Miscellaneous., 1955 (Box 10, Folder 34)
- M Miscellaneous., 1954-55 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  McGovern, John T.
- M Miscellaneous., 1953-54 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  McGovern, John T. Mohawk Airlines.
- M Miscellaneous., 1953 (Box 10, Folder 37)
- Macy Foundation., 1953 (Box 10, Folder 38)
- Middle States Association of Colleges and Secondary Schools., 1953-55 (Box 10, Folder 39)
- N Miscellaneous. National Association for the Advancement of Colored People., 1955 (Box 10, Folder 40)
- N Miscellaneous., 1954-55 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  Noyes, Nicholas H. National Thrift Committee.
- National Association of State Universities., 1954-55 (Box 10, Folder 42)
- National Commission on Accrediting., 1954-55 (Box 10, Folder 43-44)
- National Education Association., 1953-55 (Box 10, Folder 45)
- National Industrial Conference Board., 1953-55 (Box 10, Folder 46-47)
- National Planning Association., 1955 (Box 10, Folder 48-49)
  Myers, William I.; Batt, William L.
- National Reserve., 1955 (Box 10, Folder 50)
- Newcomen Society., 1951-54 (Box 10, Folder 51)
- New York State Citizens Council., 1954 (Box 10, Folder 52)
- O Miscellaneous., 1953-55 (Box 10, Folder 53)
  Olin, John M.; Farrand, Livingston; Emerson, Willard I.; Olin, Spencer T.
- P Miscellaneous., 1953-55 (Box 10, Folder 54)
  Pettit, Paul Bruce; Robertson, C. H.
- Institute of Pacific Relations., 1953-54 (Box 10, Folder 55)
- Questionnaires., 1953-54 (Box 10, Folder 56)
- R Miscellaneous. Rockwell, George H., 1954-55 (Box 10, Folder 57)
- Recommendations., 1954 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Dept. of Religion (Proposed)., 1953-54 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Rockefeller Foundation., 1953-54 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  Evans, Roger F.; Litchfield, Edward H.
- Scott Paper Company., 1955 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Selective Service and Deferments., 1953 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Sheldon Court., 1953-54 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  Morris, Evan J.
- S Miscellaneous., 1954 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  Seymour, Harold J.; Sinclair, Gregg M. Sapsucker Woods.
- Alfred P. Sloan Foundation., 1954-55 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  Zurcher, Arnold J.; Smith, Ruby Green.
- S Miscellaneous., 1954-55 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Lynah Rink., 1955 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  Carpenter, Walter S.; MacDaniels, Laurence H.
- T Miscellaneous., 1954-55 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  Telluride Association; University of Thessalonike.
- T Miscellaneous., 1953-55 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  Treman, Allan H.; Wade, Harry V. Tuskegee Institute.
- Teagle Foundation., 1954-55 (Box 11, Folder 13-16)
  Mottr Frank E.
- Walter L. Todd., 1953-55 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- U Miscellaneous., 1953-54 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  United States Steel Corporation.
- UNESCO., 1954 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- V Miscellaneous., 1953-55 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  van Wagenen, Jared.
- Visitors., 1953-54 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  Bissell, Claude T.; Bayar, Celal; Khaliq, S. G.
- Visitors., 1954-55 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- W Miscellaneous., 1954-55 (Box 11, Folder 23)
- W Miscellaneous., 1953-55 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  Wood, Frederic C. Whitney Foundation; World University Service.
- Harry V. Wade., 1953-55 (Box 11, Folder 25)
- Mary White Fund., 1954 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  White, Andrew Dickson.
- World University Service., 1953 (Box 11, Folder 27)
- XYZ Miscellaneous., 1955 (Box 11, Folder 28)
- J. L. Zwingle., 1955 (Box 11, Folder 29)
- Carbon Copies of Outgoing Correspondence of Deane W. Malott., July 1954 (Box 11, Folder 30-31)
- Carbon Copies of Outgoing Correspondence of Deane W. Malott., August 1954 (Box 11, Folder 32)
- Carbon Copies of Outgoing Correspondence of Deane W. Malott., Sept. 1954 (Box 11, Folder 33-34)
- Carbon Copies of Outgoing Correspondence of Deane W. Malott., Oct. 1954 (Box 11, Folder 35-37)
- Carbon Copies of Outgoing Correspondence of Deane W. Malott., Nov. 1954 (Box 11, Folder 38-40)
- Carbon Copies of Outgoing Correspondence of Deane W. Malott., Dec. 1954 (Box 11, Folder 41-43)
- Carbon Copies of Outgoing Correspondence of Deane W. Malott., Jan. 1955 (Box 11, Folder 44-46)
- Carbon Copies of Outgoing Correspondence of Deane W. Malott., Feb. 1955 (Box 11, Folder 47-49)
- Carbon Copies of Outgoing Correspondence of Deane W. Malott., March 1955 (Box 11, Folder 50-53)
- Carbon Copies of Outgoing Correspondence of Deane W. Malott., April 1955 (Box 11, Folder 54-57)
- Carbon Copies of Outgoing Correspondence of Deane W. Malott., May 1955 (Box 11, Folder 58-60)
- Carbon Copies of Outgoing Correspondence of Deane W. Malott., June 1955 (Box 12, Folder 1-3)
- Committee on the Revision of the University By-laws., 1955 (Box 12, Folder 4-6)
- Standing Committees, Board of Trustees., 1955 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Board of Trustees., 1955 (Box 12, Folder 8-13)
- Board of Trustees - Random Notes Letters., 1955 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Board of Trustees - Dorothy McSparran Arnold., 1954 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Board of Trustees - David P. Barr., 1954 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Board of Trustees - Neal Dow Becker., 1953-55 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Board of Trustees - Daniel J. Carey., 1953-55 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Board of Trustees - Walker L. Cisler. Fund for Peaceful Atomic Development., 1953-55 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Board of Trustees - John L. Collyer., 1953-55 (Box 12, Folder 20-21)
- Board of Trustees - Arthur H. Dean., 1954-55 (Box 12, Folder 22)
- Board of Trustees - Thomas E. Dewey., 1954 (Box 12, Folder 23)
- Board of Trustees - Mary H. Donlon., 1954-55 (Box 12, Folder 24)
- Board of Trustees - Victor Emanuel., 1953-55 (Box 12, Folder 25-27)
  Hoover, Herbert; Gannett, Frank E.; Schurman, Jacob Gould; Morrison, Philip. Communism; Jews on the Cornell University Board of Trustees.
- Board of Trustees - Horace C. Flanigan., 1953-55 (Box 12, Folder 28)
- Board of Trustees - Frank E. Gannett. Gannett Clinic; Gannett Foundation., 1953-55 (Box 12, Folder 29)
- Board of Trustees - Edwin T. Gibson., 1954 (Box 12, Folder 30)
- Board of Trustees - Stanton Griffis., 1953-54 (Box 12, Folder 31)
- Board of Trustees - Leroy R. Grumann. Grumann Squash Courts., 1953-55 (Box 12, Folder 32)
- Board of Trustees - Larry E. Gubb., 1953-55 (Box 12, Folder 33)
- Board of Trustees - W. Averell Harriman., 1955 (Box 12, Folder 34)
- Board of Trustees - Ruth Irish., 1954 (Box 12, Folder 35)
- Board of Trustees - Herbert F. Johnson., 1954-55 (Box 12, Folder 36)
- Board of Trustees - Dexter 8. Kimball., n.d. (Box 12, Folder 37)
- Board of Trustees - John S. Knight., 1954-55 (Box 12, Folder 38)
- Board of Trustees - J. Preston Levis., 1954 (Box 12, Folder 39)
- Board of Trustees - James A. McConnell., 1954 (Box 12, Folder 40)
- Board of Trustees - Albert K. Mitchell., 1953-54 (Box 12, Folder 41)
- Board of Trustees - Floyd R. Newman., 1954 (Box 12, Folder 42)
- Board of Trustees - Nicholas H. Noyes., 1953-54 (Box 12, Folder 43)
- Board of Trustees - John M. Olin., 1954-55 (Box 12, Folder 44)
- Board of Trustees - John S. Parke., 1954 (Box 12, Folder 45)
- Board of Trustees - Thomas W. Pew., 1953 (Box 12, Folder 46)
- Board of Trustees - Joseph P. Ripley., 1954-55 (Box 12, Folder 47)
  Thorp Fund.
- Board of Trustees - Francis H. Scheetz., 1953-54 (Box 12, Folder 48)
- Board of Trustees - Jacob Gould Schurman., 1954-55 (Box 12, Folder 49)
- Board of Trustees - Myron C. Taylor., 1953-54 (Box 12, Folder 50)
- Board of Trustees - Reese H. Taylor., 1953-55 (Box 12, Folder 51)
- Board of Trustees - Walter C. Teagle., 1953-55 (Box 12, Folder 52)
- Board of Trustees - Maxwell M. Upson., 1953-55 (Box 12, Folder 53)
- Board of Trustees - Elbert P. Tuttle., 1953-54 (Box 12, Folder 54)
- Board of Trustees - Ezra B. Whitman., 1955 (Box 12, Folder 55)
- Board of Trustees - Membership., 1953-54 (Box 12, Folder 56)
- Board of Trustees - Gifts to the University from Board Members., 1954 (Box 12, Folder 57)
- Board of Trustees - Agendas., 1953-54 (Box 12, Folder 58)
- Committee Appointments., 1954 (Box 12, Folder 59)
- Board of Trustees - Committees., 1954-55 (Box 12, Folder 60)
- Board of Trustees - Executive Committee., 1954-55 (Box 12, Folder 61-62)
- Board of Trustees - Investment Committee., 1954-55 (Box 12, Folder 63)
- Board of Trustees - Buildings and Grounds Committee., 1954 (Box 12, Folder 64)
- Board of Trustees - Committee on Planning and Development., 1953 (Box 12, Folder 65)
- Board of Trustees - Membership Committee., 1954 (Box 12, Folder 66)
- Board of Trustees - Committee on Finance., 1955 (Box 12, Folder 67)
- Cornell University Library Board., 1953-55 (Box 12, Folder 68)
- Board on Physical Education and Athletics., 1953-55 (Box 12, Folder 69)
- Board on Student Health and Hygiene., 1953 (Box 12, Folder 70)
- School of Nutrition Administrative Board., 1954 (Box 12, Folder 71)
- Willard Straight Hall Board of Managers., 1953-54 (Box 12, Folder 72)
- College of Architecture Council., n.d. (Box 12, Folder 73)
- College of Engineering Council., 1954 (Box 12, Folder 74-75)
- New York Hospital - Cornell Medical Center School of Nursing., 1954 (Box 12, Folder 76)
- New York State College of Agriculture and the Agricultural Experiment Stations Council., 1953-54 (Box 12, Folder 77)
- New York State College of Home Economics Council., 1955 (Box 12, Folder 78)
- New York State Veterinary College Council., 1954 (Box 12, Folder 79)
- President., 1953-54 (Box 12, Folder 80)
  Taylor, Myron C. Cornell University Council.
- President's House., 1953 (Box 12, Folder 81)
- Deans' Conference., 1953-55 (Box 12, Folder 82)
- Deans and Heads of Departments., 1954 (Box 12, Folder 83)
- Office of Public Relations and Information., 1955 (Box 12, Folder 84)
- Academic Freedom., 1953-55 (Box 12, Folder 85)
  Neufeld, Maurice F.; Lorwin, Val R.; Dunham, Barrows; Davis, Paul H. Committee on Academic Freedom and Tenure; Committee on Academic Problems Arising from Governmental Investigations.
- Academic Freedom - Clippings., 1953-55 (Box 12, Folder 86)
- "Professor X.", 1953 (Box 12, Folder 87)
  Parley, Hugh D.
- Marcus Singer., 1954-57 (Box 12, Folder 88)
  Adelmann, Howard B.; O'Leary, Paul M.
- Walter A. Snickenberger., 1953 (Box 12, Folder 89)
- Walter C. Heasley., 1955 (Box 12, Folder 90)
- President's Report., 1953-54 (Box 12, Folder 91)
- President's Office Employees., 1954 (Box 12, Folder 92)
- Deane w. Malott - speeches and Articles., 1953-55 (Box 12, Folder 93)
  Cushman, Robert E.; MacDonald, John W.; Kahin, George McT.; Baker, John C. Communism.
- "A Look Down the Future Years" by DWM., 1953 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- "UMT - A Challenge to American Thinking" by DWM., 1953 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- "Business and Industry in the Long Shadow of Education's Ills" by DWM., 1954 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Office of the Provost., 1954-55 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  Hill, F. F.
- Vice President for University Development., 1953-55 (Box 13, Folder 5-6)
  Malott, Robert H.; Cobb, H. Lyford; Dean, Arthur H.
- Committee on Student Housing., 1953-54 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  Methodist Board of Missions; Cascadilla Hall.
- Gifts., 1954-55 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  Saperstone, David A.; Queeny, Edgar M.; Dean, Arthur H.
- Gifts., 1953-55 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  Todd, Walter L.; Watzek, John W. Shackelton's Point.
- Gifts., 1954 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  Verity, Calvin; Goodnow, Walter S.; Mennen, William G.
- Gifts., 1953-54 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Robert E. Treman., 1953-55 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Collyer Boathouse., 1954-55 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Gift Reports., 1954 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Greater Cornell Fund., 1954 (Box 13, Folder 15-16)
- Cornell University Council., 1953-54 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  Grasselli, Caesar A.
- Cornell University Medical College., 1953 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Parents' Program., n.d. (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Cornell University Associates., 1953-55 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  Carlson, Eric G.; Grumann, Leroy R.; Reed, A. Bradford; Myers, William I.; Collyer, John L.
- Vice President for Research., 1954-55 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  Wright, Theodore P.; Collyer, John L.; Ward, J. Carl ton.
- Research Projects., 1953 (Box 13, Folder 22-23)
- Housing Research Center., 1952-55 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  Beyer, Glenn H.
- Brookhaven National Laboratory., 1953-54 (Box 13, Folder 25)
- Vice President for Business., 1953-55 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  Collyer, John L.; Todd, Walter L.
- Dept. of Buildings and Grounds., 1954 (Box 13, Folder 27)
- Space Use, Classroom Size., n.d. (Box 13, Folder 28)
- Vets burg., 1954-55 (Box 13, Folder 29)
- Bailey Hall., 1953 (Box 13, Folder 30)
- Campus Store., 1954 (Box 13, Folder 31)
- Safety Division., 1953-54 (Box 13, Folder 32)
- Barton Hall., 1954 (Box 13, Folder 33)
- Teagle Hall Dedication., 1954 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  Mott, Frank E.
- Teagle Hall., 1954-55 (Box 13, Folder 35)